um and I'll kind of pass the mic to Dr
Eric Mason now he'll probably teach you
more about Dr um mean brother Thunder
and um give you a little more back
history well thank y'all for having the
boldness to do this um I think it's
important to have based on the push back
I could I get it and so I think that not
only do sdas deserve a response but um I
think other believers deserve a response
to kind of the brief um part of the
video that you all posted that was um in
the in uh the real and on your
channels as you can see um they are
laying the foundation and uh Pastor Eric
Mason uh tells us that uh this video
that they're about to do is a response
is a response
so um let me address this
first
so what they said was this is going to
be response to the response videos that
were done by Adventists so I did a
response video there were there were a
lot of you know different Ministries
that were doing response videos advent's
Defense League uh did a response video
and in these response videos um so for
me in my response video uh in in two
response videos about the
scapegoat I used about a hundred
verses in my response MH and so when I
saw this come out and I heard him say a
response I was like all right well we're
about to get in the scripture right and
here's what blew my mind I'm I'm going
go back to the
screen here are the total number of
verses used by Pastor Mason and Elsie
thunder in their one hour
and 9
Minute
presentation three
verses and I want you to note where the
verses are the first verse is used by
Mason at almost 26 minutes into the
presentation the second verse at 49
minutes and 58 seconds into the
presentation and the third
verse is used by Elsie Thunder at one
minute I'm sorry one hour and 1 minute
and 37
seconds into the 1 hour and 9 Minute
presentation now I don't know about you
but for me when I heard response I
thought all right they're about to
they're about to get down in the Bible
and answer right the videos that we put
out
using strictly scripture and what I find
interesting is this idea that oh
Adventists don't go by the
Bible right uh Adventists go by Ellen
White and all their teachings are
dependent upon Ellen White and yet video
after video after video that was
presented by different Ministries
including mine as we presented we were
presenting strictly from the Bible right
strictly um you commentary and and and
people that are outside of our faith and
showing look here here is what we
believe right and so I find it
stunning that people who are saying oh
Adventists are not Bible students would
do a whole hour 9 Minute
presentation and
utilize three scriptures three
scriptures so to me that already speaks
volumes you can go back for those of you
who may not be aware of my you can go
back and actually look at my videos on
the scapegoat look at what we did on
Michael the Archangel look at what other
Ministries have done I asked ADL I just
before I got on tonight I I said uh
contacted uh Adventist Defense League
and said hey how many uh um verses did
you guys use just say for example in
your scapegoat uh in your response to
the to the to the pr to uh the Perry's
video and they said we probably used
over 100 mhm and I said
wow
so that I think that speaks volumes yes
I I think that speaks volumes but we're
going to go ahead and after we've laid
the
foundation
um I want to tell you what I think
happened here and